Finding Aid for the Jan Williams Collection of Images, 1962-2007
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Jan Williams and others, 1966-2007, II; Item 34-321
  - Jan Williams and Lennart Fessel playing percussion during a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-147)
  - Jan Williams and Fuzzy on stage during a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-148)
  - Jan Williams setting up on stage for a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-149)
  - Jan Williams and Lennart Fessel playing percussion during a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-150)
  - Jan Williams and Lennart Fessel playing percussion during a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-151)
  - Richard Dufallo conducting the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra performing Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-152)
  - Jan Williams setting up percussion instruments on stage for a performance of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-153)
  - Jan Williams setting up percussion instruments on stage for a performance of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-154)
  - Jan Williams and Lennart Fessel setting up percussion instruments on stage for a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-155)
  - Jan Williams setting up percussion instruments on stage for a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-156)
  - Jan Williams and Lennart Fessel playing percussion during a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-157)
  - Richard Dufallo conducting the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra in rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-158)
  - Richard Dufallo conducting the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra n rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-159)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-160)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-161)
  - Jan Williams and Lennart Fessel playing percussion during a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-162)
  - Jan Williams and Lennart Fessel playing percussion during a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-163)
  - Jan Williams setting up percussion instruments on stage for a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-164)
  - Richard Dufallo conducting the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra in rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-165)
  - Jan Williams and Fuzzy on stage during a rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-166)
  - Richard Dufallo conducting the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra in rehearsal of Lukas Foss' Concerto for percussion and orchestra, 1977-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-167)
  - Gideon Steiner, Bent Lylloff, and Jan Williams in Copenhagen, 1977, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-168)
  - Jan Williams and Michael Pugliese, 1979, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-169)
  - Guy Klusevec, Chester Mais, and Jan Williams, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-170)
  - Jan Williams with Bent Lylloff and Brett Dietz at Niagara Falls, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-171)
  - Jan Williams conducting Elliott Carter's Double Concerto at the Center Theater, 1979-10, 1 photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 2, Item JW-172)
  - Jan Williams, Ursula Oppens, and Paul Jacobs, 1979-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-173)
  - Jan Williams and Elliott Carter, 1979-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-174)
  - Jan Williams, Elliott Carter, Ursula Oppens, and Paul Jacobs, 1979-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-175)
  - Jan Williams and Elliott Carter, 1979-10, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-176)
  - B&W contact-sheet of 35mm images of Jan Williams conducting Elliott Carter's Double Concerto at the Pfeiffer (Center) Theater, 1979, 1 photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 2, Item JW-177)
  - Jan Williams conducting Elliott Carter's Double Concerto at the Pfeiffer (Center) Theater, 1979, 1 photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 2, Item JW-178)
  - Jan Williams conducting Elliott Carter's Double Concerto at the Pfeiffer (Center) Theater, 1979, 1 photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 2, Item JW-179)
  - Jan Williams conducting Elliott Carter's Double Concerto at the Pfeiffer (Center) Theater, 1979, 1 photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 2, Item JW-180)
  - Jan Williams playing a berimbau in Hiller's An Apotheosis of Archaeopteryx, 1981-03, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-181)
  - Jan Williams playing a berimbau in Hiller's An Apotheosis of Archaeopteryx, 1981-03, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-182)
  - Leo Smit, Jan Williams, and Diane Williams, 1982-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-183)
  - Jan Williams playing percussion at the Akademie der Künste in Berlin, 1982-09, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-184)
  - Equipment for John Cage's Atlas Eclipticalis, 1982-09, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-185)
  - Jan Williams and John Cage, 1983-04, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-186)
  - Jan Williams and John Cage, 1983-04, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-187)
  - Jan Williams and Leila Lustig, 1983-04, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-188)
  - Jan Williams and members of the UB Percussion Ensemble at the Charles Ives Center for American Music at the Canterbury School, 1983-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-189)
  - Jan Williams and members of the UB Percussion Ensemble at the Charles Ives Center for American Music at the Canterbury School, 1983-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-190)
  - Ed Folger playing percussion at the Charles Ives Center for American Music at the Canterbury School, 1983-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-191)
  - Richard Moryl, Jan Williams, Joan Moryl, and Lukas Foss outside the Charles Ives Center at the Canterbury School, 1983-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-192)
  - Jan Williams and members of the UB Percussion Ensemble at the Charles Ives Center for American Music at the Canterbury School, 1983-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-193)
  - Jan Williams and members of the UB Percussion Ensemble at the Charles Ives Center for American Music at the Canterbury School, 1983-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-194)
  - Ed Folger playing percussion at the Charles Ives Center for American Music at the Canterbury School, 1983-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-195)
  - Jan Williams and members of the UB Percussion Ensemble at the Charles Ives Center for American Music at the Canterbury School, 1983-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-196)
  - Double exposure of Jan Williams, Martin Riches, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Eberhard Blum in Berlin, with picture of Jan Williams on stage superimposed, 1984-02, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-197)
  - Jan Williams playing percussion, 1984-02, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-198)
  - Jan Williams playing percussion, 1984-02, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-199)
  - Jan Williams holding percussion mallet, 1984-02, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-200)
  - Bunita Marcus massaging the chest of Jan Williams, 1984-04, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-201)
  - Jan Williams, Eberhard Blum, and Bunita Marcus in Slee Hall, 1984-04, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-202)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, Malcolm Goldstein, Joseph Celli, David Moss, Jan Williams, Steven B. Sample, William Ortiz, and Frank Cipolla at the opening concert of the North American New Music Festival, 1985-04, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-203)
  - Eberhard Blum, Nils Vigeland, and Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's Crippled Symmetry at the Almeida Festival, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-204)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Rzewski's To the Earth at the Almeida Festival, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Ainslie, Sarah (Box 2, Item JW-205)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Rzewski's To the Earth at the Almeida Festival, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Ainslie, Sarah (Box 2, Item JW-206)
  - Jan Williams performing Nils Vigeland's Progress at the Almeida Festival, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Ainslie, Sarah (Box 2, Item JW-207)
  - Jan Williams performing Nils Vigeland's Progress at the Almeida Festival, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Ainslie, Sarah (Box 2, Item JW-208)
  - Jan Williams performing Nils Vigeland's Progress at the Almeida Festival, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Ainslie, Sarah (Box 2, Item JW-209)
  - Jan Williams performing Nils Vigeland's Progress at the Almeida Festival, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Ainslie, Sarah (Box 2, Item JW-210)
  - Jan Williams performing Nils Vigeland's Progress at the Almeida Festival, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Ainslie, Sarah (Box 2, Item JW-211)
  - Jan Williams performing Nils Vigeland's Progress at the Almeida Festival, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Ainslie, Sarah (Box 2, Item JW-212)
  - Conlon Nancarrow, Lou Harrison, and Virgil Thomson at the Almeida Festival, 1985-06, 1 photograph; Ainslie, Sarah (Box 2, Item JW-213)
  - Jan Williams and Charles Boone in Slee Hall, 1985, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-214)
  - Jan Williams and Lejaren Hiller in Warsaw, 1985-09, 1 photograph; Glanda, Andrzej (Box 2, Item JW-215)
  - Jan Williams and James Hutchinson, a U.S. Cultural Attache, in Warsaw, 1985-09, 1 photograph; Glanda, Andrzej (Box 2, Item JW-216)
  - David Del Tredici, Susan Narucki, Lukas Foss, Carol Wincenc, Jan Williams, and unidentified male at the Ojai Festival, May 1987, 1987-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-217)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams in Frankfurt with poster of concert, 1987-11, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-218)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams in Frankfurt with poster of concert, 1987-11, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-219)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams in Frankfurt with poster of concert, 1987-11, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-220)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams in Frankfurt, 1987-11, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-221)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams at a restaurant in Frankfurt, 1987-11, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-222)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, and friends at a table, eating in Berlin, 1988, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-223)
  - John Cage, Jan Williams and Jan Williams' father, Hibbard Williams, at New Music America Festival in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-224)
  - John Cage, Jan Williams and Jan Williams' father, Hibbard Williams, at New Music America Festival in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-225)
  - John Cage and Jan Williams' father, Hibbard Williams, at New Music America Festival in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-226)
  - John Cage and audience members at New Music America Festival in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-227)
  - Nils Vigeland, Madeline Burke-Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, Jan Williams, Diane Williams, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Hibbard Williams in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-228)
  - Nils Vigeland, Madeline Burke-Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, Diane Williams, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Hibbard Williams in Miami, 1988, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-229)
  - Jan Williams conducting at a school in São Paulo, 1988-06, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-230)
  - Joel Chadabe and Jan Williams rehearsing Chadabe's Another Approach to Rhythms, 1989-04, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-231)
  - Jan Williams and Orlando García together after a North American New Music Festival concert, 1990-04, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-232)
  - Orlando García, Ann Holyoke Lehmann and Eberhard Blum together after a North American New Music Festival concert, 1990-04, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-233)
  - Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's Why Patterns? for Westdeutscher Rundfunk, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-234)
  - Jan Williams, Nils Vigeland, and Eberhard Blum at Westdeutscher Rundfunk, Cologne, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-235)
  - Jan Williams portrait, Cologne, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-236)
  - Jan Williams portrait, Cologne, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-237)
  - Jan Williams portrait, Cologne, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-238)
  - Jan Williams portrait, Cologne, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-239)
  - Jan Williams portrait, Cologne, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-240)
  - Jan Williams portrait in chair, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-241)
  - Jan Williams portrait in chair, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-242)
  - Jan Williams portrait in chair, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-243)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum with bicycles in Berlin, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-244)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum with bicycles in Berlin outside building, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-245)
  - Jan Williams, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Eberhard Blum riding bikes in Berlin outside Mitropa, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-246)
  - Nils Vigeland reading and Jan Williams drinking in Berlin, 1990-09, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-247)
  - Jan Williams teaching percussion in São Paulo, 1990, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-248)
  - Jan Williams teaching percussion in São Paulo with student on stage, 1990, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-249)
  - Joel Chadabe with computer in Copenhagen, 1990, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-250)
  - Jan Williams conducting Koussevitzky's Concerto for Double Bass and Orchestra with Clark Suttle and the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1990-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-251)
  - Jan Williams conducting Koussevitzky's Concerto for Double Bass and Orchestra with the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1990-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-252)
  - Jan Williams conducting Koussevitzky's Concerto for Double Bass and Orchestra with Clark Suttle and the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1990-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-253)
  - Jan Williams conducting Koussevitzky's Concerto for Double Bass and Orchestra with Clark Suttle and the Sjelland Symphony Orchestra, 1990-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-254)
  - Jan Williams and friends at the Dublin City Gallery The Hugh Lane, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-255)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum in front of a statue in Dublin, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-256)
  - Jan Williams, Nils Vigeland, and Eberhard Blum at a restaurant in Dublin, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-257)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum in front of posters in Dublin, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-258)
  - Jan Williams and Eberhard Blum in Dublin, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-259)
  - Jan Williams, Martin Riches, Eva Züchner, Eberhard Blum, Steffen Schleiermacher, and two unidentified males outside the Dublin City Gallery The Hugh Lane, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-260)
  - Jan Williams with Ann Holyoke Lehmann, Eberhard Blum, Steffen Schleiermacher, Eva Züchner, Martin Riches, and other friends in Dublin, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-261)
  - Steffen Schliermacher, Jan Williams, and Eberhard Blum bowing after a performance at the Dublin City Gallery The Hugh Lane, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-262)
  - Steffen Schliermacher, Jan Williams, and Eberhard Blum performing at the Dublin City Gallery The Hugh Lane, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-263)
  - Jan Williams playing percussion at a rehearsal at the Dublin City Gallery The Hugh Lane, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Lehmann, Ann Holyoke, 1951- (Box 2, Item JW-264)
  - Steffen Schliermacher, Jan Williams, and Eberhard Blum rehearsing at the Dublin City Gallery The Hugh Lane, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-265)
  - Steffen Schliermacher, Jan Williams, and Eberhard Blum rehearsing at the Dublin City Gallery The Hugh Lane, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-266)
  - Jan Williams, Ann Holyoke Lehmann, and Bernard --? at the Dublin City Gallery The Hugh Lane, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-267)
  - Jan Williams, Eberhard Blum, and Bernard --? at the Dublin City Gallery The Hugh Lane, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-268)
  - Jan Williams, Eberhard Blum, and Emmett Williams in Dublin, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-269)
  - Ann Holyoke Lehmann kissing Jan Williams, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-270)
  - Ann Holyoke Lehmann kissing Jan Williams, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-271)
  - Jan Williams, Eberhard Blum, Martin Riches, and Emmett Williams at the Dublin City Gallery The Hugh Lane, 1991-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-272)
  - Jan Williams and Werner X. Uehlinger at hat-ART recording session for Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston Sessions, 1991-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-273)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams performing Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston at a recording session for hat-ART records, 1991-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-274)
  - Nils Vigeland at hat-ART recording session for Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston, 1991-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-275)
  - Art Lang, Peter Pfister, and Werner X. Uehlinger at hat-ART recording session of Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston, 1991-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-276)
  - Jan Williams during hat-ART recording of Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston, 1991-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-277)
  - Jan Williams during hat-ART recording of Morton Feldman's For Philip Guston, 1991-08, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-278)
  - Eberhard Blum, Elizabeth Williams, and Jan Williams in Berlin, 1993, 1 photograph; Brown, Earle, 1926-2002 (Box 2, Item JW-279)
  - Eberhard Blum and Jan Williams in Berlin, 1993, 1 photograph; Brown, Earle, 1926-2002 (Box 2, Item JW-280)
  - Ann Holyoke Lehmann and Jan Williams in Berlin, 1993, 1 photograph; Brown, Earle, 1926-2002 (Box 2, Item JW-281)
  - Earle Brown, Jan Williams, and Eberhard Blum in Berlin, 1993, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-282)
  - Poster for the New York School concert in Berlin, 1993, 1 photograph; Brown, Earle, 1926-2002 (Box 2, Item JW-283)
  - Eberhard Blum, Christian Wolff, Roland Dahinden, Jan Williams, and Steffen Schleiermacher at rehearsal of Christian Wolff's Exercises, 1994-04, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-284)
  - Nils, Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams in Gütersloh, Germany, undated, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-285)
  - Eberhard Blum, Nils Vigeland, and Jan Williams at a piano during rehearsal of For Philip Gustin by Morton Feldman, 1995-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-286)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's For Philip Gustin, 1995-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-287)
  - Nils Vigeland, Eberhard Blum, and Jan Williams rehearsing Morton Feldman's For Philip Gustin, 1995-01, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-288)
  - Jan Williams and Nestor Astuti in Buenos Aires, 1996-11, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-289)
  - Room with instruments and chairs at Percussive Arts Society International Convention, 1999, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-290)
  - Jan Williams with Gary Rutkowski, John Bacon Jr., and Bob Accurso at the Percussive Arts Society International Convention, 1999, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item JW-291)
  - Jan Williams with the NEXUS Percussion Ensemble at the OJAI Festival after a performance of Les Noces, 2007-06, 1 photograph; Millard, Robert (Box 2, Item JW-292)
  - Ed Burnham at performance at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1967?, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-293)
  - Andrew White playing English horn at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1967?, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-294)
  - Rehearsal in old Baird Hall, Room 101, with Stanley Silverman, Karl Kraber, and Sherman Friedland, 1964, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-295)
  - Rehearsal in old Baird Hall, Room 101, with Charles Joseph, Jean Dupouy, and Jay Humeston, 1964, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-296)
  - Ed Burnham playing percussion at a performance at the Albright-Knox Art Gallery, 1967?, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-297)
  - John Rowland preparing for rehearsal of John Cage's Concerto for Prepared Piano at Kleinhans Music Hall, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-298)
  - John Cage conducting his Concerto for Prepared Piano with Lukas Foss at the piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-299)
  - John Cage conducting his Concerto for Prepared Piano with Lukas Foss at the piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-300)
  - John Cage conducting his Concerto for Prepared Piano with Lukas Foss at the piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-301)
  - John Cage conducting his Concerto for Prepared Piano with Lukas Foss at the piano, 1967-05, 1 photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item JW-302)